Guide to the George McTurnan Kahin papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
Kahin, George McTurnan papers, [ca. 1945-2000]
- Series III. Correspondence
  - Alphabetical Correspondence (by individual)
    - General correspondence, 1968-77 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Merle Ricklefs correspondence, 1968-77 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - J. Norman Parmer correspondence, 1966-75 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - G. Pauker correspondence, 1968-77 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Charles Pepper correspondence, 1967-69 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - James A. Perkins correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Julia Petrova correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Cao Ngoc Phuong correspondence, 1972-86 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Pham Huy Thong correspondence, 1973-80 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Jan M. Pluvier correspondence, 1986-88 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Porter correspondence, 1978-84 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Gary Porter correspondence, 1970-76 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Gary Porter correspondence, 1980-89 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Robert Pringle correspondence, 1968-73 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Robert Pringle correspondence, 1978-79 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Donald Ranared & Marcus Raskin correspondence, 1974-88 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Felix Reichmann correspondence, 1969-88 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Robert C. Rice correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1966-68 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Mark Roelofs correspondence, 1973-75 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Mohamad Roem correspondence, 1967-72 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Judith Rosenberg, 1955-56 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - General correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Huot Sambath correspondence, 1968-70 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Kernail Samdu correspondence, 1973-75 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Dr. A. Sartono Kartodirdjo & Robert A. Scalapino correspondence, 1966-72 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Frank Sieverts correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Chris Sugnet correspondence, 1982-86 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Surachart correspondence, 1980-87 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Scarborough correspondence, 1975-76 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - David Schoenbrun correspondence, 1967-75 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Josef Silverstein correspondence, 1955-57 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Josef Silverstein correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Singapore University & ISEAS, 1985-89 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - S.E.A.D.A.G., 1967-73 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - S.E.A.P. Thursday Luncheon Notices, 1970-72 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence, 1965-75 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Ida Shadily care Krug correspondence, 1967-76 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Sabam Siagian correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Lauriston Sharp correspondence, 1967-73 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Siegal, Sie Kwat Soen, Nim Chee Siew & Siagian correspondence, 1967-71 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Siegelman correspondence, 1972-76 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Norodom Sihanouk correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - General Simatupang correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Stephen Sloan (Cornell paper), 1966-75 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - John Smail correspondence, 1958-88 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Datus C. Smith correspondence, 1967-74 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Roger Smith correspondence, 1960-75 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Theodore Smith correspondence, 1973-76 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Pamela Sodhy correspondence, 1973-90 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Soedjatmoko correspondence, 1960-70 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Mary Somers correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Eugene Staples correspondence, 1954-73 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - General Suhud correspondence, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Cleon O. Swayzee correspondence, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Robert Henry Taylor correspondence, 1971-76 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Tang Tsou correspondence, 1962-68 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Nguyen Thai correspondence, 1965-72 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Nguyen Thi Thanh correspondence, 1982-90 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Thak Chaloemtiarana correspondence, 1975-77 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Robert O. Tilman correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Iwan Tirtaamidjaja correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Tran van Dinh correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Truong Buu Lam correspondence, 1973-76 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Frank Underhill correspondence, 1966-76 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Dixon Underwood correspondence, 1972-68 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Esta Unger correspondence, 1980-82 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Robert Van Niel correspondence, 1960-71 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Indian Minority (Kartomo Vasil), 1955-56 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Vlastos, Van der Veur & Doering correspondence, 1978-90 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Vo Van Ai correspondence, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Vu van Thai correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - General correspondence, 1968-75 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - General correspondence, 1967-77 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - General correspondence, 1966-73 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Wang Gung-Wu correspondence, 1967-73 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Francis E. Ward correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Ingrid Wessel correspondence, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Frank Weinstein correspondence, 1969-74 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Jayne Werner correspondence, 1969-75 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Daphre Whittam correspondence, 1960-62 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Widjojo Nitisastro correspondence, 1966-69 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - A & G Williams correspondence, 1956-74 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - David A. Wilson correspondence, 1955-73 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Winarti Partaningrat correspondence, 1966-68 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Wood & Wolters correspondence, 1967-75 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Alex Woodside correspondence, 1972-74 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Yad Project, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Xue Mou Hong correspondence, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - David Wurfel correspondence, 1956-73 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Clemont Zablocki correspondence, 1965-68 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - General correspondence (X, Y and Z), 1966-77 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - General correspondence (X, Y and Z), 1957-64 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Alphabetical Correspondence (general)
    - Correspondence (A), 1967-77 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence (A continued), 1967-77 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence (A additional), 1956-59 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (B), 1967-77 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence (B continued), 1966-75 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence (B additional), 1955-61 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (C), 1966-75 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence (C continued), 1963-77 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence (C continued), 1967-78 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (C additional), 1954-59 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (D), 1966-76 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (D continued), 1966-75 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (D additional), 1955-59 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (E), 1966-79 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (E & F additional), 1954-59 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (F), 1954-75 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (F continued), 1961-77 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (G), 1966-77 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (G continued), 1967-75 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (G continued), 1968-76 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (G additional), 1956-59 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (H), 1966-76 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (H continued), 1966-77 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (H continued), 1966-77 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (H continued), 1966-75 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (H additional), 1956-59 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (I), 1966-74 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (I & J additional), 1954-59 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (J), 1966-76 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (J continued), 1967-77 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (K), 1963-77 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (K continued), 1965-77 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (K additional), 1956-58 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (L), 1966-75 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (L additional), 1953-59 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (Mc), 1966-75 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (M-Mn), 1963-80 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (Mo-Mz), 1966-79 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (M additional), 1956-59 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (N-Ne), 1966-76 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence (Ne-Nz), 1967-76 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (O), 1966-73 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (O, P, Q additional), 1955-59 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Padaminata correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (P), 1966-74 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (P continued), 1964-77 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Quinn correspondence, 1968-72 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (R), 1967-79 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (R continued), 1966-77 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (R additional), 1954-60 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (So-Sz), 1966-76 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (So-Sz continued), 1966-77 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (S additional), 1955-58 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (T), 1966-77 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (T additional), 1955-59 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (U), 1966-81 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (U additional), 1956-58 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (V), 1966-75 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (V additional), 1955-59 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (W), 1955-59 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (X, Y, Z), 1956-58 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Additional Correspondence
    - Lauress Ackman correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Stanley Sanders Bedlington correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - David Bellerose correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bill Berry correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Vincent Boudreau correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Thomas Branan correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Eugene Bruns correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Eugene Bruns correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - John Dennis correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Piel Nguyen Thi Dieu correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Dhakidae correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Ford Foundation, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ford Foundation, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ford Foundation, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Fulbright application, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Herbert Feith correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Herbert Feith correspondence, 1970-80 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Herbert Feith correspondence, 1962-64 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Mark Dion correspondence, 1965-70 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - David Elliot correspondence, 1975-80 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Bryan David correspondence, 1989-97 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Fulbright materials, 1962-63 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - David Honkel & Fatimah Hashinz correspondence (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Gunung Agung correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Random Correspondence (H), 1954-64 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Random Correspondence (H), 1955-65 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Robert Hackenberg correspondence, 1955-61 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Dr. T. Hadiwidjaja correspondence, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - D. G. E. Hall correspondence, 1957-64 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - John S. Harris correspondence, 1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Newspaper clippings on communism In Indonesia (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Mai V. Elliot correspondence, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Rough draft papers (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Mohammad Hatta correspondence, 1954-65 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Rita E. Hauser correspondence, 1962-64 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Samuel P. Hayes correspondence, 1960-62 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Everett Hawkins correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Hazel Pembangunan correspondence, 1957-60 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Harold Hinton correspondence, 1958-60 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Michael Harris correspondence, 1956-63 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Harvard University Press, 1957-64 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Steve Heder correspondence, 1980-87 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Stever Heder correspondence (continued), 1977-84 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Mary F. Heidhues correspondence, 1960-66 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mohammad Hatta correspondence, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Benjamin Higgins correspondence, 1954-62 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Donald Hindley correspondence, 1958-64 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Roger Hillsman correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Jiro Hirano correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - William L. Holland correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - William C. Hollinger correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - P. J. Honey correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - C. Hooykaas correspondence, 1954-65 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Dick Hopper correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - John Howard correspondence, 1957-65 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Al & Judy Hudson correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Random Correspondence (I), 1960-65 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Indonesian Embassy and Consulate, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Edward Ingraham correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Omas T. Ihromi correspondence, 1961-63 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Nobutaka Ike correspondence, 1954-64 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Yoichi Itagaki correspondence, 1956-63 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Random correspondence (J), 1960-65 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Robert Jay correspondence, 1956-61 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Quing-Guo Jia correspondence, 1983-87 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Quing-Guo Jia correspondence (continued), 1986 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Tony Johns correspondence, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Ladd I. Johnson correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - George Kanahele correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Roy Jumper correspondence, 1957-65 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - R. B. Jones correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Howard Jones correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Umar Kayam correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Kartomo correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Garth N. Jones correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Bernard Kalb correspondence, 1959-62 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Random correspondence (K), 1954-66 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Koentjaraningrat correspondence, 1957-67 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Koentjaraningrat correspondence, 1962-66 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Koentjaraningrat correspondence (Hudson & Oosterwal), 1965-66 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Koentjaraningrat correspondence (C. U. press and Palmer), 1964-66 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Koichi Kishi correspondence, 1956-64 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Government 314 materials, 1956-66 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Konuma correspondence, 1974-77 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Random correspondence (L), 1960-65 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Robert L. Lambright correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - O. Latimore correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Edward Lee correspondence, 1980-89 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - John Ledge correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Michael Leifer correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Michael Leigh correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Daniel Lev correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Daniel Lev correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Julia Levtonova correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - John W. Lewis correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - P. E. Lilienthal correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Shannon Loane correspondence, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Lockhart correspondence, 1984-88 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Francis Kok Wah Loh correspondence, 1974-81 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Franklin Long correspondence, 1960-66 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Random correspondence (M), 1954-63 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Random correspondence (M continued), 1960-65 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - McConnell & McCray correspondence, 1957-65 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Thomas R. McHale correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Charles b. McLane correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Ko Khin Maung Kyi correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Charles F. Keyes correspondence, 1962-64 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - J. A. C. Mackie correspondence, 1959-65 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Charles P. McVicker correspondence, 1959-63 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Ruth McVey correspondence, 1954-59 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Ruth McVey correspondence, 1958-59 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Ruth McVey correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Ruth McVey correspondence, 1960-61 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Malaysian Sociological research Institute, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - J. Rita Marsland & Deane W. Malott correspondence, 1954-66 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Jay Maryanov correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Josef Mestenhauser correspondence, 1958-60 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Burhan Magenda correspondence, 1975-86 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Burhan Magenda correspondence (continued), 1978-88 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Burhan Magenda correspondence (continued), 1974-84 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Hiroshi Matsumoto correspondence, 1976-89 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Microfilming project, 1963-65 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Frank Miller correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - R. S. Milne correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Francis E. Mineka & Moekarto Notowidigdo correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Random correspondence (M), 1975-80 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Dolina Miller correspondence, 1977-81 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Eric Morris correspondence, 1972-80 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Summer Seminar, 1965-66 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1960's (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1960's (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1960's (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1960's (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Ward Morehouse correspondence, 1960's (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Phillip Mosely correspondence, 1956-61 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Arthur T. Mosher correspondence, 1957-61 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - David Mozingo correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Lloyed Musolf correspondence, 1954-63 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Dr. Hla Myint correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Random correspondence (N), 1960-77 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Akira Nagazumi correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - General Nasution correspondence, 1960-65 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - National Science Foundation, 1960-64 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Mohammad Natsir correspondence, 1954-57 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Naval War College, 1963-64 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Noto Soeroto (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Ngo-Ton-Dat correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Norman K. Nicholson correspondence, 1961-67 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - S. Nishijima correspondence, 1955-63 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Don O. Noel correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Nugroho correspondence, 1957-62 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Random correspondence (N), 1959-78 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Stan O'Connor correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Giok Po Oey correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Milton E. Osborne correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Random correspondence (P), 1956-65 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Roger Paget correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - L. N. Palar correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Leslie Palmier correspondence, 1956-64 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Richard L. Park correspondence, 1958-63 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - J. Norman Parmer correspondence, 1952-65 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Guy J. Pauker correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Winarti Partaningrat correspondence, 1958-65 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Peace Corps, 1961-64 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Karl J. Pelzer correspondence, 1954-64 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Donald Pond correspondence, 1960-63 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Donald Pond correspondence (continued), 1964-65 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Robert Pringle correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Random correspondence (Q), 1960 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Random correspondence (P), 1956-65 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Random correspondence (P), 1986-87 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Felix Reichmann correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - G. J. Resink correspondence, 1955-64 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Ralph Retzlaff correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Victor Reynolds correspondence, 1955-63 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Robert C. Rice correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Audrey Richey correspondence, 1963-66 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Rockefeller/Philippines, 1963-66 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Marvin L. Rogers correspondence, 1959-64 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Rockefeller Foundation-general materials, 1962-65 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Phyllis Rolnick correspondence, 1957-65 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Phyllis Rolnick correspondence (continued) (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Phyllis Rolnick materials (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Jusuf Ronodipuro correspondence, 1956-63 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Saul Rose correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Clinton Rossiter correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Random correspondence (S), 1954-64 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Random correspondence (S continued), 1960-65 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Random correspondence (S continued), 1963-65 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Random correspondence (S continued), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Milton Sacks correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Josef Silverstein correspondence, 1955-65 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Edward Sinaga correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Pandam Siswoharsojo correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - William Skinner correspondence, 1957-63 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - William Skinner correspondence (continued), 1951-54 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - William Skinner correspondence (continued), 1955-57 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - John W. Smail correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - John & Laura Smail correspondence, 1958-63 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mohammad Sadli correspondence, 1957-64 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Khalid B. Sayeed correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Robert Scalapino correspondence, 1954-65 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Robert Scigliano correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Arthur Schiller correspondence, 1955-60 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Hans Schmitt correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Hassan Shadily correspondence, 1956-65 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Lauriston Sharp correspondence, 1954-64 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - James Siegal correspondence, 1961-65 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Siew Nim Chee correspondence, 1957-64 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Jerry Silverman correspondence, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Soelaeman Someardi correspondence, 1956-60 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence (continued), 1962-64 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence (continued), 1961-62 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence (continued), 1960-61 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Selo Soemardjan correspondence (continued), 1957-59 (Box 20, Folder 23)